(Silence; Operating Room Area)
=Stand Up for Love=
=Episode 6=
Jiang Lai.
Did Zhang Haotian
hurt you?
How about
we try another way?
I'm fine.
Don't worry about me.
It's just that scumbag
grabbed me and kissed me
a couple of times.
It's no big deal.
Besides,
he sees me as Zhao Ke now.
I should be happy, shouldn't I?
You should be happy too.
Jiang Lai.
When did you become so overprotective?
Like you asked,
I took the photos.
But I want to destroy them.
We'll find another way.
I sent them to Su Qinglan.
Makes the game more interesting,
doesn't it?
Haotian is in North America right now.
These photos were clearly taken here
in China.
Someone is obviously trying
to frame him.
It must be someone competing with him.
Haotian would never betray me.
Mr. Li.
Ms. Su.
Lulu is just too innocent.
She won't listen no matter what I say.
What about the kidney donor?
How is the investigation going?
Ms. Su,
we've obtained all the hospital records.
The donor's name was Jiang Lai.
The records state
that it was a voluntary,
unpaid donation.
There was no sign of coercion
or any transaction.
(Zhang Haotian is a nobody.)
(He has no connections or background.)
(How could he have found)
(a matching kidney so quickly?)
(This is definitely not a coincidence.)
(I won't let Lulu)
(fall into the hands of someone
like him.)
You've been keeping an eye
on Zhao Ke lately.
You probably haven't had much time
for Lin Lulu.
I told her there was urgent work
to handle in North America.
I won't be back for a month.
Aren't you afraid this will blow up
in your face?
You and Lin Lulu have
a prenuptial agreement.
I'm just saying, what if...
what if she kicks you out?
Then all our efforts will have been
for nothing.
You're worrying too much.
I'm flying back from North America
today.
I'll give her a surprise.
The longer we wait,
the more risks we take.
We should get her to steal
the prenuptial agreement
from Su Qinglan as soon as possible.
Got it.
Do you still have enough money?
Do you need me to...
Being Lin Lulu's husband
makes it easy for me
to secure investments.
Once I have the funds, I can keep
the investors I lured in before.
Those investors will come back
and invest even more.
For this 20-million-yuan project,
I'll put in 10 million first.
I'll put in the remaining 10 million
once the project is about to launch.
Sure. Then stay with me
for two more days.
Mr. Zhang.
Perhaps we should discuss this again.
When you turned me down, Ms. Shen,
I already made myself clear.
The offer won't be on the table forever.
I know you have
the Lin family's backing.
What if I add another ten million?
(I love you, Lin Lulu!)
Baby.
(Zhang Haotian❤Lin Lulu)
I bought you
that Ferrari you wanted.
Honey.
Yeah?
I love you so much.
Don't worry.
There won't be any problems.
(The prenuptial agreement has to go.)
Honey, when are you coming home?
I miss you so much.
Baby, it'll still be a while
before I can come back.
Where are you?
Honey.
Baby.
I miss you like crazy.
Did you bring me a gift?
Guess.
(Condom)
What does this mean?
This is your gift.
You think I need this as a gift?
I want to have a baby with you now.
You don't want a child with me?
Say something, Zhang Haotian.
Say it!
I don't want our child
to grow up in a family
where the father isn't accepted.
That's not real love.
And it's not a real family.
It wouldn't be fair to the child.
A father who isn't accepted?
I knew it.
The prenuptial agreement
my mom made you sign...
I knew it would make you overthink.
Your mother only did it
for your own good.
For my own good?
If she really cared about me,
we would've gotten married a year ago.
Why wait until now?
You signed it, fine.
But she even locked the agreement away.
Who is she trying to protect it from?
Is this for me?
Do you like it?
I love it.
You're the best.
(I can't just sit here and wait.)
(I need to do something else
to speed things up.)
(Driving a Wedge)
♪Listen, the wind chimes softly whisper♪
♪I should forget you♪
♪But I have the will,
yet not the strength♪
♪To carry on♪
♪The scenery you once longed to see♪
♪You no longer have the strength♪
♪You want me to go there for you♪
♪I look up and see a hollow sky♪
♪Your freedom♪
♪Has become my cage♪
♪My hand brushes over your smile
in the photograph♪
♪This glass of wine is filled
with sorrow♪
♪I look up at the beautiful night sky♪
♪You told me♪
♪I would shine like a star♪
♪But you forgot to teach me♪
♪How to live without you♪
♪I look up at the starry sky♪
♪So hazy and blurred♪